applicationsearch.net 2011-10-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for applicationsearch.net.

Last updated March 20, 2011. 

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this Website and any content, products or services made available from or through this website including any sub domains thereof ("Website"). The operator of the Website is referred to as "Company."

By visiting this Website and requesting information, products or services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as they may be amended from time to time. As Company updates or expands its Website, services or products, this Privacy Policy may change and the changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. Company does not provide notice of changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this Website. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Website Terms and Conditions which govern your use of this Website in general.

This Website is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. The Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.

Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices.

#### 1.0. Collection of Information.

1.1. User Direct Information. Each time you provide or transmit information via the Website, Company may obtain and collect personal information about you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, credit card information, bank account information and telephone or cell phone number (collectively referred to as "Personal Information"). 

1.2. Other Methods of Collecting Personal Information. Other occasions when Company obtains information from you include: (1) when you claim a prize or seek to redeem an offer by Company or by a third party; (2) when you request assistance through Company's customer service department; and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a Company service or newsletter. 

1.3. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. Company currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, Company may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future. 

(a) Cookies. "Cookies" are a feature in your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of Company's websites, you need to accept cookies. 

(b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Company to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Company also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Company's database. 

(c) IP Addresses. Company automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages. 

(d) Computer Profiles. Company may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, Company may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. 

(e) Data Analysis. Data Analysis technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of Company. 

(f) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, Company strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology. 

1.3. No Information Collected from Children. Company will never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of 13. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. 

1.4. Credit Card Information and Bank Account Information. Company may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers, bank account information and related information when an individual places an order on Company's Website. When the credit card or bank account information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Company will use the credit card information or bank account information for purposes of processing and completing the transaction you requested on the Website, and the credit card information or bank account information will be disclosed to third parties as necessary to complete the requested purchase transaction. 

#### 2.0. Use of Personal Information.

2.1. Third Party Offers. Company may provide your Personal Information to third parties with whom they have a business relationship for the purposes of securing the services and products you have requested or provide you with additional marketing materials from which you may choose additional products or services. Company may make your Personal Information available to companies or other entities not affiliated with the Company that have goods, services and offers that might be of interest to you so that they may send you these offers.

2.2. Email and Unsubscribe Policy. Company uses Personal Information to provide third party promotional offers by email to individuals. Company may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Company's email lists, unsubscribe visit http://www.applicationsearch.net/landing/misc/unsubscribe.php or click on the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email received from us.

2.3. Content of Email Messages. You may receive certain commercial email messages sent by third parties for products which may be of interest to you. In such case, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" and the email will have a method at the bottom of the email to unsubscribe from that Advertiser. Company is not responsible for third party emails sent to you.

2.4. Targeted Advertising. Company may use Personal Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Company uses Technology Information to associate an individual with that person's Personal Information, and Company attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2.5. Telemarketing. Company may use Personal Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. You may have your telephone number or cell phone number listed on a state or federal do not call registry. By registering and using this Site, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 §CFR 310 et seq. (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, you have authorized us to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Website or other advertisement media made available by us (e.g., email marketing), you agree that such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and you may be contacted via email, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR. We may use Personal Information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.

2.6. Wireless Addresses. If the e-mail address you provide to Company is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Company or its business associates (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

2.7. Short Message Service. Company may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. In addition to any fee of which you are notified your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. Company will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. Company may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. We may also access the content of your account and wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and service-related complaints.

You may remove your information from Company's database. If you remove your information from Company's database it will no longer be used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by visiting http://www.applicationsearch.net/landing/misc/unsubscribe.php or by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.

2.8. Use of Technology Information. Company may use Technology Information (1) to match a person's Personal Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Personal Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Company's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps Company to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Company can target advertising and promotions to them.

2.9. Technical Service Providers. Company may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These third party's may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Company may also use third parties to help operate our Website, deliver products and services, and Company may share your Personal Information with such third parties for our business (such as Website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these parties do not have any right to use the Personal Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us. When you conduct e-commerce with one of the e-commerce affiliates or service providers to which the Website may be linked, certain Personal Information such as your e-mail and home address may be collected by the service provider's server and made available to us.

2.9.1. Complying with Legal Process. Company will use or disclose your Personal Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with Company. Company will use and disclose your Personal Information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of Company , its owners, or those of Company 's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Company's acceptable use policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes.

#### 3.0. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

3.1. Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the websites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

3.2. Links. The websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

3.3. Affiliations/Merger/Sale. Company further reserves the right to disclose, transfer or sell your Personal Information to companies who are affiliated with Company in Company's sole discretion. If Company changes ownership through an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of business status, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the right to use your Personal Information collected from the Website.

#### 4.0. Foreign use of the Website.

To the extent that you are accessing the Website while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Personal Information you are providing Company is collected and stored in the United States and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States.

#### 5.0 Security

We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information. When you submit information at the website, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store Personal Information are kept in a secure physical environment. Company has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, Company uses Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although Company takes reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, Company cannot and does not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our website is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.

#### 6.0 Choice/Opt-out

Company provides you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when it asks for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotions, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

Customer Care Contact Information: http://www.applicationsearch.net/landing/misc/unsubscribe.php

#### 8.0. California User Consumer Rights. 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have provided Personal Information to Company or third parties under a list management arrangement with Company to request certain information regarding Company's disclosure of such information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of Personal Information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this section. If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at http://www.applicationsearch.net/landing/misc/feedback.php. 

2011 **_Applicationsearch.net_**. All Rights Reserved.
